pazbookbiz.com 2013-12-13

# Privacy Policy | Paz and Associates

Respect for the privacy, security, and confidentiality of clients is our utmost concern. The purpose of this privacy policy is to let you know how we use personal information collected via website, phone or fax. Please note that the practices set forth in this privacy policy apply to Paz & Associates only. If you link to other web sites or talk with other vendors, please review their own respective privacy policies.

**Collection of Information**  
When voluntarily submitted by visitors to our website, we collect certain information like names, postal addresses, email addresses, phone number, etc. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request or order, and allows us to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with book industry-related organizations or our training partners, who may or may not use the information for marketing purposes. We may also share information when trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only Paz & Associates representatives and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All communications via Constant Contact allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: dpaz@pazbookbiz.com  
By Phone: (904) 277-2664

Thank you for placing your trust and confidence in Paz & Associates to facilitate your bookstore dreams.
